E: Nice shirt.
But I’m not sure about those sneakers.
B: Hey, Izzy!
Yeah, I’m with Emma.
We’re going for a walk…Yeah…Yeah…
So do you want to come and meet us?
Oh.
OK.
See you later.
Izzy’s working from home today.
E: On a Saturday?
B: Yeah.
E: What a surprise.
Anyway…How are things with you?
B: Izzy’s doing really well at the new job.
I think they’re going to give her a promotion.
And she’s looking at new apartments, too.
E: OK, that’s how Izzy’s doing.
I asked about you.
B: Well, I’m fine.
E: Yeah, sure you are.
B: What do you mean by that?
E: It’s just…everything seems to be about Izzy right now.
Her new job.
Her new apartment.
Her new life.
Make sure there’s enough room for you, too.
B: There is enough room for me.
We’re OK.
I mean, I’m OK.
She’s just busy right now.
E: You don’t spend enough time together.
B: Well, we’re going to go away for a weekend soon.
Just the two of us.
When she’s less busy.
E: And when she gets this promotion, is she going to be less busy and have more time for you?
B: Wait.
I know where we are.
Just around the corner.
Come on.
E: Ben.
What a cute store.
B: Yeah, it’s great.
I came here once with Izzy.
Do you want to go in?
E: Sure.
But you haven’t answered my question.